{
  "adultsonly": [
    {
      "Question": "Areodjarekput Is An Inuit Word That Means",
      "Answer": "To Exchange Wives For A Few Days"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Bow-Wow, Ding-Dong And Pooh-Pooh Are All Names For",
      "Answer": "Different Theories On The Origin Of Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Charged Chambers And Birds’ Nests Are Two Euphimisms For The Female Genitals As Penned By This Man",
      "Answer": "William Shakespeare"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Coprophobia Is",
      "Answer": "The Fear Of Feces"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cypridophobia Is",
      "Answer": "The Fear Of Prostitutes"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hamesucken Is",
      "Answer": "The Crime Of Assaulting Someone In Their Own Home"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Lanugo Is",
      "Answer": "The Fine Hair Covering A Fetus"
    },
    {
      "Question": "No-Pan Kissa Is A Japanese Term For Cafes In Which",
      "Answer": "The Floors Are Mirrored And The Waitresses Wear No Underwear"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pediophobia Is",
      "Answer": "The Fear Of Dolls"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Peladophobia Is",
      "Answer": "The Fear Of Bald People"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pentheraphobia Is The Fear Of",
      "Answer": "Your Mother-in-law"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pissenlit, The French Word For Dandelion, Means",
      "Answer": "Piss The Bed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Puppetry Of The Penis Began At The Melbourne International Comedy Festival And Consists Of",
      "Answer": "Nude Men Making A Variety Of Shapes With Their Penises"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Quaquaversal Means",
      "Answer": "Going Off In All Directions"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Skookum Describes Something That Is",
      "Answer": "Impressive And First-rate"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Smegma Is Latin For",
      "Answer": "Detergent"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Thwarterous Means",
      "Answer": "Twisted"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Shirime Is A Japanese Monster With An Eye In Place Of",
      "Answer": "An Anus"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Spermologer Is A Person Who",
      "Answer": "Collects Trivia And Current News"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Squintifego Is",
      "Answer": "A Person Who Squints A Lot"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Stoop-Gallant Is Another Word For",
      "Answer": "A Disease Or Illness"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Tooting-Glass Is Another Word For",
      "Answer": "A Mirror"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Birth Control Method Used By Ancient Greeks Was For A Woman To Hold Her Breath, Squat, And",
      "Answer": "Sneeze"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Bite From The Brazilian Wandering Spider Causes This To Happen For Several Hours",
      "Answer": "An Erection"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Mahoohoo Is",
      "Answer": "An African White Rhinoceros"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Man In California Sued Bmw Because A Four-Hour Ride On The Motorcycle Did This",
      "Answer": "Gave Him An Erection For 20 Months"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Melcryptovestimentaphiliac Is Someone Who",
      "Answer": "Compulsively Steals Women’s Underwear"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Pig’s Penis Is Shaped Like",
      "Answer": "A Corkscrew"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Renifleur Is Someone Who",
      "Answer": "Gets Sexual Pleasure From Smells"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Sea Cucumber Eats With",
      "Answer": "Its Anus"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Tappen Is A Leafy Plug Used To",
      "Answer": "Seal A Bear’s Bottom For The Winter"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Type Of Fruit Fly Called The Drosophila Bifurca Is Known For Having",
      "Answer": "Sperm That’s Six Centimeters Long"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Unique Feature Of An Alligator’s Penis Is That It’s",
      "Answer": "Permanently Erect"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Whale’s Penis Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Dork"
    },
    {
      "Question": "According To A 1986 Gallup Poll, The Most Immoral Thing A Person Could Do Was",
      "Answer": "Lie About A Sexual Disease"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Agalmatophilia Is A Sexual Fetish Describing People Are People Who Are Sexually Attracted To",
      "Answer": "Mannequins"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Alfred Kinsey Could Insert This Into His Penis",
      "Answer": "A Toothbrush"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Amoxaxia Is The Name Of The Fetish Of",
      "Answer": "Having Sex In Parked Cars"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Applying This To A Woman’s Lips Can Help Them Relax And Assist In The Regulation Of Their Menstrual Cycles",
      "Answer": "A Man’s Underarm Sweat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Archaeologists In Cyprus Found A 7Th-Century Lead Tablet With This Curse Written On It:",
      "Answer": "May Your Penis Hurt When You Make Love"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Artists In Ancient China Would Often Paint Scenes Of Nakedness, But Would Not Depict This",
      "Answer": "A Bare Female Foot"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Astroglide Lubricant Was Accidentally Invented In 1977 By Two Men Attempting To Develop",
      "Answer": "A Space Shuttle Cooling System"
    },
    {
      "Question": "At The End Of Roman Mime Plays, Audiences Could Demand That The Female Lead Do This",
      "Answer": "Strip On Stage"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Benito Mussolini Warded Off The Evil Eye By",
      "Answer": "Touching His Testicles"
    },
    {
      "Question": "British Spies Stopped Using Semen As Invisible Ink Because",
      "Answer": "It Started To Smell Bad When It Wasn’t Fresh"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Buckingham Palace Was Constructed On The Site Of",
      "Answer": "A Brothel"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cactus, Raw Horseflesh, Pit Viper, Goat, Charcoal, Collagen, And Viagra Are All Japanese",
      "Answer": "Ice Cream Flavors"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Capuchin Monkeys Will Usually Say Hello By Doing This",
      "Answer": "Showing Off Their Erections"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cardinal Wolsey Was Accused Of Giving Syphilis To Henry Viii By",
      "Answer": "Whispering In His Ear"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Clinton, Montana Hosts An Annual Testicle Festival Called",
      "Answer": "Testy Fest"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Define Crapulous",
      "Answer": "Relating To Drunkenness"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Define A Pussyvan",
      "Answer": "A Temper"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Define A Snoutfair",
      "Answer": "A Good-looking Person"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Define The Word Gymnophoria",
      "Answer": "The Sense That Someone Is Undressing You In Their Mind"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Diphallia Is A Condition In Which A Man",
      "Answer": "Is Born With Two Penises"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Dragonflies Have Penises Shaped Like Shovels That Are Used To",
      "Answer": "Scoop Out Their Rival’s Sperm"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Each Time A Snow Flea Jumps, A Sac Comes Out Of Its Anus That",
      "Answer": "Acts Like An Airbag To Absorb The Shock When They Land"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Early Naturalists Believed That A Male Opossum Mated With A Female’s",
      "Answer": "Nose"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Egyptian Pharaohs Ritually Did This To Ensure An Abundance Of Water",
      "Answer": "Masturbated Into The Nile"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Empress Isabelle Of Bavaria Bathed In",
      "Answer": "Strawberry Juice"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ernest Shackleton Took This With Him To The Antarctic To Combat Snow Blindness",
      "Answer": "Cocaine"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Every Time They Have Sex, Some Sea Slugs Use A New",
      "Answer": "Penis"
    },
    {
      "Question": "F. Scott Fitzgerald And Dostoyevsky Both Had",
      "Answer": "Foot Fetishes"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Featuring A Drawing Of A Snowman, This Patent By Dawn Goll Is For",
      "Answer": "Decorative Penis Covers"
    },
    {
      "Question": "For Tax Purposes In Norway, Stripping Is Considered",
      "Answer": "An Art Form"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Formicophilia Is Sexual Arousal From",
      "Answer": "Small Insects Or Worms Moving And Nibbling On Your Body"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Fruit Bats Enjoy Sexual Pleasure From",
      "Answer": "Fellatio"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Guess The Title Of The Movie Centered On A Forgetful Father Who Tries To Carry Out The Tradition Of Burying His Son’s Circumcised Foreskin",
      "Answer": "Dad On The Run"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Howard Hughes’s Aversion To Pet Dogs Began In 1940 When",
      "Answer": "A Dog Bit His Penis"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Iantronudia Is The Name Of A Fetish For Men And Women Who Become Sexually Aroused After",
      "Answer": "Getting Naked In Front Of A Medical Professional"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If A Person Is Gambrinous, It Means They",
      "Answer": "Are Full Of Beer"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Have A Venereal Disease In Nebraska, You May Not Do This",
      "Answer": "Get Married"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Have Algolagnia, You Are Someone Who",
      "Answer": "Is Both Masochistic And Sadistic"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Have Jumentous Urine, You Have",
      "Answer": "Strong-smelling Urine That’s The Color Of A Horse’s"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Have Kleptolagnia, You Are Someone Who",
      "Answer": "Is Aroused By Theft"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Like Endytophilia, You Enjoy Having Sex While",
      "Answer": "Still Dressed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Should Find Yourself In Sweden About To Have Sex, But Without Protection, For A Small Fee You Can",
      "Answer": "Call The Condom Ambulance"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Suffer From Oneirogmophobia, You Are Afraid Of",
      "Answer": "Wet Dreams"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Wanted To Test A Woman’s Fertility During The 16Th Century, You Could Insert A Garlic Clove Into Her Vagina –She Was Deemed Fertile If Twelve Hours Later",
      "Answer": "Her Breath Smelled Like Garlic"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You’re Suffering From Sphenopalatine Ganglioneuralgia, You Have",
      "Answer": "An Ice Cream Brain Freeze"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 1367, King Charles V Of France Banned The Wearing Of Penis-Shaped",
      "Answer": "Shoes"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 1930, A Radium-Infused Jockstrap With This Name Went On The Market, Claiming To Boost Sexual Potency",
      "Answer": "The Scrotal Radiendocrinator"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 1992, Fertility Doctor Cecil B. Jacobson Was Imprisoned For Doing This To As Many As 75 Of His Patients",
      "Answer": "Impregnating Them With His Own Sperm"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 1998, Charles Shoemaker Ii Patented This Article Of Fashion",
      "Answer": "A Mistletoe Belt Buckle"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 2001, Wesley Johnson Patented This Item For Men",
      "Answer": "A Lap Dance Liner To Be Worn Under Pants"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 2006 Jan Vinzenz Krause Invented A Prototype For",
      "Answer": "A Spray-on Condom"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Ambon, Indonesia, Men Run Through The Fields Naked And Ejaculating In Order To",
      "Answer": "Ensure A Good Clove Crop"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In California It Is Prohibited To Vend These Within One Thousand Feet Of Any County Highway",
      "Answer": "Boobie Pillows"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Colombia, A Man Is Required To Have Sex With A Guajiro Woman If She Can Succesfully Do This During A Cermonial Dance",
      "Answer": "Trip Him"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In England In 1558, These Were Taxed According To Length",
      "Answer": "Beards"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In England, A Pregnant Woman Can Legally Do This To A Policeman’s Helmet",
      "Answer": "Relieve Herself In It"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, It’s Illegal To Have Sex In A Toll Booth With",
      "Answer": "A Truck Driver"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Japan, Tintin Is Pronounced Chin-Chin And Means",
      "Answer": "Penis"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Liverpool, England, It Is Legal For A Woman To Be Topless If She Is A Clerk In This Location",
      "Answer": "A Tropical Fish Store"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In One Sentence, Describe The Plot Of The Movie Bad Johnson",
      "Answer": "A Man Wakes Up To Find That His Penis Has Come To Life In Human Form And Is Trying To Steal His Girlfriend"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Order To Remain Legal, Porn Shops In India Are Called",
      "Answer": "Museums"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In The 18Th Century, A Penis Was Commonly Referred To As A",
      "Answer": "Whore Pipe"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In The 1999 Tour De France, Mario Cipollini Taped A Photo Of Pamela Anderson To His Handlebars In Order To Do This",
      "Answer": "Boost His Testosterone Levels"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In The 19Th-Century Versions Of Cinderella, Her Sisters Called Her This",
      "Answer": "Cinder-slut"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In The Early 16 Century In Europe, A Brothel Was Referred To As",
      "Answer": "A Nunnery"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In The Final Stages Of A Hidatsa Woman’s Pregnancy, It Is Socially Acceptable For Her Husband To",
      "Answer": "Have Sex With Her Sister"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Victorian Times It Was Thought That Bathing In This Would Help Women Shrink Flabby Breasts",
      "Answer": "Fresh Strawberries"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Willowdale, Oregon, It’s Illegal For Men To Do This To Their Wives During Intercourse",
      "Answer": "Talk Dirty"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ithyphallophobia Is The Fear Of",
      "Answer": "Thinking About Or Having An Erect Penis"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Johnny Cash Was Left With An Addiction To Painkillers After He Was",
      "Answer": "Attacked By An Ostrich"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Kaufmich.Com In Germany Announced In 2015 That It Was Hiring A Full-Time",
      "Answer": "Prostitute Tester"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Koro Is A Disorder Found In Southeast Asia In Which A Boy Or Man Believes This",
      "Answer": "That His Penis Is Shrinking And Will Soon Disappear"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Lava Lamps Were Invented By An Accountant Whose Hobby Was Making",
      "Answer": "Underwater Nudist Films"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Male Elephants Use Their Penises Daily To",
      "Answer": "Swat Flies"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mark Sturkenboom, A Dutch Designer, Created A Dildo Containing This Special Feature",
      "Answer": "A Mini-urn To Hold The Remains Of A Loved One"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mice Do This While Having Sex",
      "Answer": "Sing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mice Enjoy The Smell Of This Illegal Substance",
      "Answer": "Marijuana"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Moby Dick Was Based On A Real Sperm Whale Called",
      "Answer": "Mocha Dick"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Monkeys Will Pay To Look At This",
      "Answer": "Porn"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Moose Masturbate By",
      "Answer": "Rubbing Their Antlers On Trees"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Moths Can Confuse A Bat’s Ultrasound By Doing This",
      "Answer": "Wiggling Their Genitals"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Oculolinctus Is A Fetish In Which People Are Sexually Aroused By",
      "Answer": "Licking Eyeballs"
    },
    {
      "Question": "On The King’s Birthday In Thailand, Men Get In Lines Over 1,000 People Long To Get",
      "Answer": "Free Vasectomies"
    },
    {
      "Question": "One In Every 5,000 Babies Is Born Without One And Must Have It Created In The Hospital",
      "Answer": "An Anus"
    },
    {
      "Question": "One Of D.H. Lawrence’s Pastimes Was Taking Off His Clothes And",
      "Answer": "Climbing Mulberry Trees"
    },
    {
      "Question": "One Of Shakespeares Euphemisms For Infidelity Was Groping For…",
      "Answer": "Trouts In A Peculiar River"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Oscar Nominees In 2014 Took Home Goodie Bags Including A Rather Intimate Voucher For",
      "Answer": "A Vaginal Rejuvenation Procedure"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Outside Of Uppsala In Sweden, You Can Take A Stroll In Djuprven, Which Means",
      "Answer": "Deep Arse"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pharaohs Employed Slaves To Watch Over Their Wine And",
      "Answer": "Fan It To Keep It Cool"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Physicians Did This In 16-Century France To Help Cure Hysteria In Women",
      "Answer": "Pulled Out Their Pubic Hair"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pregnant Bee Wolves Tending To Their Nest Have Been Known To Do This To Male Bee Wolves Looking To Copulate",
      "Answer": "Sting Them To Death"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pteronophobia Is The Fear Of",
      "Answer": "Being Tickled By Feathers"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ren Descartes Had A Fetish For",
      "Answer": "Cross-eyed Women"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Selling Illegal Cigarettes In The Us Is Known By The Police As",
      "Answer": "Smurfing"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Sigmund Freud’s First Research Project Was On",
      "Answer": "The Sex Life Of The Eel"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Sob Lake In Canada Was Originally Called",
      "Answer": "Son Of A Bitch Lake"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Someone Who Is Matutinal Is",
      "Answer": "Breezy And Bright In The Morning"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Someone Who Is Cock-Throppled Has",
      "Answer": "A Really Prominent Adam’s Apple"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Spermophobia Is The Fear Of",
      "Answer": "Germs"
    },
    {
      "Question": "State Officials In New Mexico Ordered 400 Words Of Sexually Explicit Material To Be Cut From This Document",
      "Answer": "Romeo And Juliet"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Malleus Maleficarum, A 15Th-Century Witchcraft Treatise, Warned That Witches Stole Men’s Penises And",
      "Answer": "Kept Them In Birds’ Nests"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Amazonian Munduruku Tribe Refers To Intercourse As The Act Of",
      "Answer": "Eating Penises"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Ancient Greek City Of Megara Held A Version Of The Olympic Games That Included A Boys-Only",
      "Answer": "Kissing Contest"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Australian Beer Company, Foster’s, Is The World’s Second-Largest Producer Of",
      "Answer": "Wine"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Aztec Emperor Montezuma Drank 50 Cups Of This Each Day Before Visiting His Harem",
      "Answer": "Chocolate"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The British Slang For Watching Or Enaging In Sexual Acts In Public Is",
      "Answer": "Dogging"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Cherokee Word For The Female Genitalia Is Tupuli, Which Literally Translated Means",
      "Answer": "Feathered Flying Serpent"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Christian Polemicist Tertullian Thought That Swallowing During Fellatio Was An Act Of",
      "Answer": "Cannabilism"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Company Fastsize Invented A Device Called The Eqm, Which Stands For",
      "Answer": "Erectile Quality Monitor"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Cornish Word For Breath Is",
      "Answer": "Anal"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Costliest Sex Position That Ancient Greek Prostitutes Offered Was Keles, Meaning",
      "Answer": "The Racehorse"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The English Word Fascinate Shares Its Origin With The Latin Fascinum, Which Was",
      "Answer": "A Phallus Worn Around The Neck To Ward Off Evil"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The First Ad For A Personal Vibrator Was Published In 1899, Promising To Cure",
      "Answer": "Wrinkles, Headaches And Female Hysteria"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The First Film To Show The Act Of Sex In 1932 Was",
      "Answer": "Extase"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The First Maturbate-A-Thon In Europe Was Held In London In Order To",
      "Answer": "Raise Money For Charity"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The First Maturbate-A-Thon In Europe, Held In London, Was Also Called The",
      "Answer": "Wank-a-thon"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The First People To Have Bachelor Parties Were",
      "Answer": "Spartan Soldiers"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The German Word For Contraceptive Is",
      "Answer": "Schwangerschaftsverhtungsmittel"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Inflexible Gloves That Astronauts Wear Causes",
      "Answer": "Their Fingernails To Fall Off"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Japanese Word For Poverty Is",
      "Answer": "Bimbo"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Male Capuchin Monkey Will Have Sex With Any Female Capuchin Monkey That Does This",
      "Answer": "Throws A Stone At Him"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Mormon Church Has A Website To Help Its Members Determine Appropriate",
      "Answer": "Underwear"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Name Of A Retired Major League Baseball Hitter And Outfielder Who Played For The White Sox, Twins And Tigers",
      "Answer": "Rusty Kuntz"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Penis Of A Mole Shrew Is Shaped Like This",
      "Answer": "The Letter S"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Penis Of The Abyssinian Bat Is Covered With",
      "Answer": "Stiff Bristles"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Penises Of The Bushmen In The Kalahari Desert Are",
      "Answer": "Always Erect"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Poke-Me-Boy Tree Only Grows Here",
      "Answer": "The Virgin Islands"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Right Testicle Typically Hangs Lower In Men Who Are",
      "Answer": "Left-handed"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The River With The Largest Discharge Volume In Albania Is Called",
      "Answer": "The Seman"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Sanskrit Word For Vagina",
      "Answer": "Yoni"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Second Episode Of The Muppets Was Called",
      "Answer": "Sex And Violence"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Strongest Creatures On Earth That Can Pull 100,000 Times Their Own Body Weight Are",
      "Answer": "Gonorrhea Bacteria"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Term Venereal Disease Comes From A Latin Phrase Morbus Veneris, Meaning",
      "Answer": "The Sickness Of Venus"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The U.S. Patent And Trademark Office Originally Denied Sanderson And Brady’s Application For This Product",
      "Answer": "Edible Underwear"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Uk Porn Industry Hosts An Annual Awards Ceremony Called",
      "Answer": "The Shaftas"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Walibri Tribe In Central Australia Do This As A Greeting",
      "Answer": "Shake Their Penises"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Widespread Infertility Of Spanish Women In 1709 Was Believed To Be Due To",
      "Answer": "Singing During Sex"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Word Gymnasium Originates From The Word Gymnazein In Greek, Meaning",
      "Answer": "To Exercise Naked"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Word Masturbation Originates From A Latin Word That Means",
      "Answer": "To Pollute Oneself"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Word Scumbag Originally Referred To This",
      "Answer": "A Used Condom"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Word Yonic Means",
      "Answer": "In The Shape Of A Vulva"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Word Pencil Comes From A Latin Word Meaning",
      "Answer": "Small Penis"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The World’s First Female Interactive Sex Robot Is Called",
      "Answer": "Roxxxy"
    },
    {
      "Question": "There Are 11 Places Found In Utah, With Varying Spellings, That Are Called",
      "Answer": "Molly’s Nipple"
    },
    {
      "Question": "There Is A Painting Hanging In The Louvre By One Of Da Vinci’s Pupils Which Depicts",
      "Answer": "A Naked Mona Lisa"
    },
    {
      "Question": "There Is A Unique Brewer In Oregon Who Makes Beer From Yeast Collected From",
      "Answer": "His Own Beard"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Theresa Berkley Was A 19Th-Century English Dominatrix Who Designed A Flogging Rack Called",
      "Answer": "The Berkley Horse"
    },
    {
      "Question": "These Were Invented To Protect German Soldiers From Stds During World War Ii",
      "Answer": "Sex Dolls"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This British Last Name Is Four Times Less Common Today Than It Was In 1881",
      "Answer": "Cock"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Is The Name Of The Guide Book Of In-Car Sex Positions",
      "Answer": "Carma Sutra"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Is The Name Of The Vietnamese Fish Whose Penis Resides Under Its Chin",
      "Answer": "The Phallostethus Cuulong"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Late 1800S Word Means Addicted To Whoremongering",
      "Answer": "Pornerastic"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Man Carried A Hip Flask Full Of Wine Infused With Cocaine",
      "Answer": "Pope Leo Xiii"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Man First Discovered That An Erect Penis Is Filled With Blood, Not Air",
      "Answer": "Leonardo Da Vinci"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Person Owns The Crypt Next To Marilyn Monroe’s",
      "Answer": "Hugh Hefner"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Plant Was Considered Sexually Sacred By The Druids",
      "Answer": "Mistletoe"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Scent Is Irresistible To Female Goats In Heat",
      "Answer": "Human Body Odor"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Sex Toy Was Invented By A Tibetan Monk",
      "Answer": "The French Tickler"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Six-Inch Creature Has A Penis Over Thirty-Two Inches Long",
      "Answer": "The Alpine Banana Slug"
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Word Comes From The Nahuatl Word For Testicle",
      "Answer": "Avocado"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Those With Dendrophilia Enjoy",
      "Answer": "Trees As Sex Partners"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Tim Patch, The Australian Artist Who Paints Landscapes And Portraits With His Penis, Often Goes By His Stage Name,",
      "Answer": "Pricasso"
    },
    {
      "Question": "To Honor The Professor Who Coined The Expression, The G-Spot Was Almost Called This",
      "Answer": "The Whipple Tickle"
    },
    {
      "Question": "To Try Avoiding Being Eaten By Its Mate, A Male Orb-Web Spider Has Genitals That",
      "Answer": "Detach And Keep Pumping While He Runs Away"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Tsar Peter Iii Declined To Consummate His Marriage To Princess Sophie In Favor Of Doing This",
      "Answer": "Playing With His Toy Soldiers"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ukrainian Scientist Grigoriy Chausovskiy Invented This Product",
      "Answer": "A Musical Condom"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Until 2001, While Dressing In Character, Disneyland Employees Weren’t Allowed To",
      "Answer": "Wear Their Own Underwear"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Used By Egyptians In 2000 B.C., This Was The First Known Contraceptive",
      "Answer": "Crocodile Dung"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Used By Women During Court In Georgian England, A Bourdaloue Was",
      "Answer": "An Object Squeezed Between The Thighs To Urinate Into"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Venustraphobia Is The Fear Of",
      "Answer": "Beautiful Women"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Viagra Was Originally Developed To Treat This",
      "Answer": "Angina"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Victor Hugo Recorded Of All The Women He Slept With By",
      "Answer": "Making Detailed Erotic Drawings"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What Does A.N.U.S Stand For?",
      "Answer": "American Nihilistic Underground Society"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When A Male Drone Mates With The Queen, This Occurs",
      "Answer": "His Testicles Explode And He Dies"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Germans Pose For Photos, They Say",
      "Answer": "Ant Shit"
    },
    {
      "Question": "William Masters And Virginia Johnson Met While",
      "Answer": "Studying How People Reach An Orgasm"
    },
    {
      "Question": "You Can Find This On A Slug’s Head",
      "Answer": "Its Anus"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Your Hair Does This When You’re Anticipating Sex",
      "Answer": "Grows More Quickly"
    }
  ]
}